ChunYu Chang

Odenton, MD mr91217@gmail.com 3013677975

My name is ChunYu Chang, an United States citizen, 33 years old. I am a self-motivated, high sense of responsibility and honest person. I like learning new skills to improve myself. It could be tough to settle in a new different career at beginning but I always keep positive and try my best to face any assignment.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Part Time Employee

Macy's - Bethesda, MD May 2019 to March 2020

became a part time associate and transfer to a different store for studying new skills, python, data science and machine learning.

Fulfillment Team Lead

Macy's - Virgilina, VA November 2015 to May 2019

- 1. improve the business goal
- 2. supervise and improve the shipping progress and quality
- 3. manage team's schedule
- 4. training new fulfillment associates

Store Supervisor

CHI-BA Technology CO.LTD - Chiayi March 2008 to June 2013

- 1. sell cellphones
- 2. sell plans with cellphones
- 3. repair cellphones

Education

boot camp in web developer

The George Washington University - Arlington, VA May 2021 to October 2021

secondary language in English

Maryland English Institute of Maryland University - College Park, MD January 2014 to January 2015

Bachelor's in Biomechatronic

National Chiayi University - Chiayi

June 2006 to June 2012

Skills

- Python (1 year)
- AWS (Less than 1 year)
- Microsoft Word (3 years)
- Microsoft Powerpoint (3 years)
- Excel (3 years)
- Data Science (Less than 1 year)
- Machine Learning (Less than 1 year)
- Django (Less than 1 year)
- Web design (Less than 1 year)
- Web development (Less than 1 year)
- HTML5
- JavaScript
- CSS
- SOL
- React
- MySQL
- Node.js (Less than 1 year)
- Express.js (Less than 1 year)
- NoSQL (Less than 1 year)

Military Service

Branch: NAVY

Service Country: Taiwan

Rank: soldier

June 2007 to June 2008

Certifications and Licenses

UDEMY Python for Data Science and Machine Learning Bootcamp

October 2020 to Present

Montgomery College Python Prgramming

July 2019 to Present

UDEMY Python and Django Full Stack Web Developer Bootcamp

March 2021 to Present

GW boot camp web development

October 2021 to Present